http://www.arbias.org.au/index.php/about-us/privacy-policy.html

Translate site through Google
Search
Search ...
Skip to content
Skip to site navigation
HomeAbout UsVisionStrategic PlanHistoryOrganisational ChartExecutive Managersarbias Service User CouncilGovernanceLifetime FriendsAnnual ReportsHR StrategyQuality FrameworkComplaintsPartnersPrivacy PolicyServicesVictoriaHousingCommunity ProgramsNeuropsychology (NPAIS)NDIS Services TAC Intensive Outreach Case ManagementNew South WalesAccessClinical Neuropsychology & Behavioural InterventionNeuropsychological AssessmentsCorrective Services NSW InformationPublicationsGeneral InformationTrainingVictoria and NSWResearchEmploymentWorking for arbiasCurrent VacanciesContact Us
About UsVisionStrategic PlanHistoryOrganisational ChartExecutive Managersarbias Service User CouncilGovernanceLifetime FriendsAnnual ReportsHR StrategyQuality FrameworkComplaintsPartnersPrivacy Policy
Enabling our
people &
partners to achieve their
very best
HomeAbout UsPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting the arbias web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for the arbias web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors, or when you make bookings or purchases through this arbias web site. The information you provide is only used to fulfil your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
The site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help customize the site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us directly via:
e-mail: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Phone: +61 3 8388 1222
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
HomeAbout UsServicesInformationTrainingResearchEmploymentContact Us
